

AMANDA FOSTER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with over 16 years professional experience in the real estate industry. Strong analytical planning and problem solving skills needed to solve challenging real-world problems through code. Dedicated to lifelong learning and collaboration to further develop my skills and make a difference to a project and a team.

EXPERIENCE

PRESENTLY MEDIA **FOUNDER**

San Diego | 2018-Present

- Design and create WordPress websites, logos and branding
- Establish social media accounts and branding
- Build e-commerce stores including WordPress with WooCommerce integration. Etsy shop set up and integration
- Specialize in Print On Demand store models

DRATA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Remote | 2/2021 - 3/2021

- Advanced security technology for continuous SOC 2 compliance
- Full Stack Web Development internship focused on React, NestJS and MySQL
- Integrating websocket technology using Pusher to existing internal

CHAMBERLAIN PROPERTY MANAGEMENT PROPERTY MANAGER

Carlsbad | 2013-2020

- Managed a portfolio of 80-100 single family homes and condos
- Managed 64 unit apartment community
- Developed and implemented streamlined processes and procedures company wide for property inspections.
- Built strong trusting relationships with owners and tenants
- Determined scope, planning, scheduling, coordinating and oversight of full renovation projects

EDUCATION/TRAINING

LEARN ACADEMY

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

Remote | 2020-2021

INDEPENDENT STUDY

Udemy I 2018 to Present

- Web Developer Bootcamp Colt Steele
- Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp Colt Steele
- Modern JavaScript Bootcamp Colt Steele
- React Front To Back Brad Traversy
- MERN Stack Front To Back Brad Traversy
- React JS | Essentials / Hooks Thomas Weibenfalk

Palomar College | 1993-1995

• General Studies - 54 Credits Completed

AKFosterDev.com



AKFosterDev@gmail.com





San Diego, CA (Remote)







LANGUAGES

JAVASCRIPT / ES6 | RUBY HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS

FRAMEWORKS|LIBRARIES

REACTJS | NODEJS | EXPRESSJS RUBY ON RAILS | BOOTSTRAP

DATABASES

MONGODB | POSTGRESQL | MYSQL

TESTING

JEST | ENZYME | RSPEC

OTHER

GIT/GITHUB | REST API | AJAX | JSON AGILE DEVELOPMENT | SCRUM PAIR AND MOB PROGRAMMING NETLIFY | HEROKU

SKILLS

PROJECT PLANNING & MANAGEMENT LEADERSHIP | COLLABORATION ORGANIZATION | DIAGNOSTICS COMMUNICATION | NEGOTIATION ADAPTABLE | ANALYTICAL | DETAILED